<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rioacha</string>
    <string name="action_settings">About Tourism</string>
    <string name="about">Riohacha Tourism app \n Developed by Diego Bañol \n Asesored by Edwin Cubillos</string>
    <string name="intro">Riohacha.\n Its beauty is synonymous of exuberance, the exotic prevails </string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="dinners">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="sites">Tourist Sites</string>
    <string name="info">Demographic Information</string>
    <string name="aboutus">About the App</string>
    <string name="demo">The town ofRiohacha has a population of 167.865 people \n These 137.629 lives in urban zone and 30.236 in rural zone \n Riohacha has in mayorty indian population, Riohacha has 33.647 Wayuu Indian \n and 9.900 Wiwa and Kogui indian population</string>
    <string name="hotel1">Waya Guajira</string>
    <string name="hotel2">Taroa</string>
    <string name="hotel3">PLaya La Roca</string>
    <string name="hotel4">Mendihuaca Caribbean Resort</string>
    <string name="ihotel1">We are located in the heart of la Guajira. Our guest enjoying a unique experience of know the essence of the Wayuu culture</string>
    <string name="ihotel2">Taroa Lifestyle Hotel represents the new concept of boutique hotels : small, intimate , modern and economic , emphasizing the care and quality in each of their services.</string>
    <string name="ihotel3">This exceptional location easily accessible to visitors, combines the tropical rainforest with endless kilometers of white sandy beaches and warm sea , in a magical setting supported by the ancestral legacy of the ancient Tayrona</string>
    <string name="ihotel4">This combination between nature and comfort of a hotel, allows us to offer our guests spacious and comfortable villas for 2 , 4 and 6, recreational activities inside the hotel, variety of food.</string>
    <string name="bar1">La Casa del Marisco</string>
    <string name="bar2">Yotojoro</string>
    <string name="bar3">KnoafoodyDrink</string>
    <string name="bar4">La Morena</string>
    <string name="ibar1">Generous portions and good atmosphere. The place is clean and has a good reputation</string>
    <string name="ibar2">The yotojoro restaurant " Cactus Heart " in Wayuunaiki. It offers seafood delicacies , Monsignor snapper is exquisite , lemonade and coconut seafood casseroles are simply delicious</string>
    <string name="ibar3">Drinks and delicious meals. The barman , chef and waiters are offering the best service.</string>
    <string name="ibar4">It is a restaurant bar with a quiet atmosphere, good music , good service, and very tasty food</string>
    <string name="site1">Puente del Rito</string>
    <string name="site2">Muelle</string>
    <string name="site3">Plaza de Padilla</string>
    <string name="site4">Monumento a francisco el hombre</string>
    <string name="site5">Paseo de la playa</string>
    <string name="isite1">Cooled by the trade winds from the north, this bridge is located at the mouth of the River Rancheria . From there you can see a beautiful sunset.</string>
    <string name="isite2">It was built in 1937 and has 12,000 meters long. It is made by a beautiful travel where tourists enjoy the gentle breeze.</string>
    <string name="isite3">It is the favorite meeting place for the riohacheros to enjoy the sunset . Within its beautiful architecture is a monument to Admiral Padilla.</string>
    <string name="isite4">Are located in the Round Point of the street 15</string>
    <string name="isite5">Extends for all de 1a street. While you walk you can find little shops of sea food</string>
</resources>
